人人影視
YYeTs.com
本字幕由人人影視字幕組翻譯
禁止用作任何商業盈利行為
翻譯： 暴龍蛋      圈圈      阿髻
翻譯： 蘇小黛      Kiko      DustD      胖兔純
時間軸： 濃子   萌    校對： 胖兔純
后期： 孤帆    總監： 米小勒   胖兔純
塞勒姆
第一季  第十三集
《塞勒姆》前情提要
Previously on Salem.
我不走
I won't go.
審判的結局只有上絞刑架
But a trial will result with you in the gallows.
約翰·奧登是我的朋友  可能是我唯一的朋友
John Alden is my friend, perhaps my only one.
你會讓友情
And you would allow friendship
阻擋你自我提升的步伐嗎
to stand in the way of your own elevation?
他是無辜的
He is innocent.
你渴望約翰·奧登能活下來
You do want John Alden to live.
那個面具的能力
That the power of that mask
只能被一種人所激活
can only be accessed by those of one kind.
你是說我是...
Are you saying that I am...
是個巫師
A witch.
你曾發誓她們會安全的
You swore that they would be safe,
但是她們死了
but they're dead!
召集年輕人
Gather the young,
窮人  痛苦之人
the poor, the suffering.
他們將會作為我們的軍隊
They will be our army.
你知道要怎么做吧
You know what to do with it?
這世上仍有你我的容身之處
There is still a place for us in this world.
只有在夢里
Only in dreams.
與我一起做個美夢吧
Dream with me.
你是他們中的一員嗎
You're one of them?
現在你知道了
Now you know.
知道什么
Know what?
知道你是個巫師嗎
That you -- you're a witch?
是的  我是巫師
Yes. A witch.
現在你應該繼續前行
You should just keep going now.
我們時間不多了
We don't have much time.
我還是得知道
I still need to know.
為什么
Why?
為了生存
Survival.
我只希望你好好活著  快走吧
All I want is for you to save yourself, so go.
你只要知道我仍然愛著你
Believe that I still love you enough
只要知道你活著我就滿足了
to simply be satisfied knowing you survive,
即使那意味著我可能再也見不到你
even if that means I'm never gonna see you again.
它又回到我手上了
It came back to me.
正如你又回到了我身邊
As you came back to me.
萬物歸宗
All things return,
就像每一滴眼淚最終歸于大海
like every salty tear returns to the sea.
這是我所學到的
This is something one learns.
作為巫師嗎
As a witch?
作為女人
As a woman.
我父親曾說
You know, my father said
這是重生之地
this was the land of second chances.
這是我們的重生之地
So this is ours.
我們可以重新開始
We could start again.
我們只需要離開這兒
All we have to do is walk away.
你不明白
You don't understand.
他們不會允許的  我...
They'd never let me. I --
那你就留下來
Then stay.
你可以選擇
You have a choice.
無論你不得不做的是什么
What you have to do, whatever it is,
你真的能開心嗎
will it really make you happy?
我不知道
I don't know.
我想你知道
I think you do.
我想你跟我一樣清楚
I think you know as well as I do
你的心里從未有過像今天一樣的平靜
that there'll be no peace in your heart like there is today.
我從不知道平靜是種什么感覺
My heart has never known peace.
也許吧  只是也許
Then maybe, just maybe,
我們會一起發現的
We'll find it together.
好  我跟你走
All right. I'll come.
但有件事兒我必須先去了結了
But there's something I must do first.
如果我不回去解決它
If I don't go back and fix it,
會有大事兒發生的
terrible things will happen.
這是我的誓言
This is my vow.
月上樹梢頭之前
I will meet you here
我會來這找你
before the moon rises above those trees --
我發誓
I swear it.
好的
Okay.
但一旦時間過了
But when the moon goes, I go...
不管你回沒回來  我都會走
with or without you.
我會回來的
I shall be back.
好的
All right.
*擂我戰鼓*
*Pound me the witch drums*
*鼓鳴震天*
*Witch drums*
*擂我戰鼓*
*Pound me the witch drums*
*鼓鳴震天*
*The witch drums*
*寧入地獄*
*Better pray for hell*
*不留人間*
*Not hallelujah*
給你的
A tribute.
貢品
For you.
給你的  我的女王
For you, my queen.
梅西
Mercy.
塞勒姆眾多迷失的靈魂中
Of all the lost souls in salem,
我最同情你
I pity yours most of all.
親愛的  我對你做了什么
My dear, what have I done to you?
你對我做了什么
What have you done to me?
你背叛了我
You have betrayed me.
我從未想背叛你  梅西
It was never my intention to betray you, Mercy.
我從你眼中看到了自己的影子
I saw myself in your eyes,
我知道一無所有  一無是處的感覺
knew what it was like to have nothing, be nothing,
我想讓你有更大的成就
and I wanted so much more for you.
所以我把你想要的給了你
So I gave you what you wished for,
但是我警告過你
but I warned you.
不  我沒想讓我的朋友被害死
No, I didn't wish for my friends to be killed.
我承諾保證她們的安全
I promised them that they would be safe...
都是因為你  你答應過我
Because you -- you promised me.
但是你欺騙了我
But you lied.
你說謊
You lied.
現在她們都死了
And now they are all dead.
你所說的一切都是謊言
Everything that comes from your lips is a lie.
是謊言
It's a lie.
謊言  謊言
Lies! Lies!
謊言
Lies!
-梅西  -此時此地不要找我了
- Mercy? - Don't look for me now, not here.
你不會找到我的
You won't find me.
但是我會在你最不想被找到時找到你
But I will find you when you least want to be found.
艾薩克
Isaac.
你也是來幫他們摧毀我的思想嗎
Have you come to help dismantle my mind?
他們就是在干這個嗎
Is that what they're doing?
對  確實是
Yes...in effect.
受我父親之命
On my father's order --
這是他愿意重新接納我的條件
His condition for accepting me back into the flock.
我所有的收藏
All my collection,
所有無用之理的工具
all the tools of useless reason...
除了一樣
...all but one.
父親說我必須重回一切知識的開端
My father says I must return to the beginning of all knowledge.
作為我迷失和恥辱的獎賞
As a reward for my loss and my humiliation,
他允許我跟他一起回波士頓
I am to be allowed to return with him to Boston.
艾薩克啊
Oh, Isaac.
這會兒你來找我干什么
What do you want with me in this,
在我受辱的這一時刻
the hour of my abasement?
我不知道你的話是什么意思  先生
I don't know what that means, sir.
我是來跟你說奧登上尉的事
But I came to say something about captain Alden.
他今天就要被絞死了
He is to be hung today.
但你們兩個人是朋友
But you two were friends.
你可能從未這樣說過  但我知道
You might never have said so, but I know so.
而且我相信  今生今世
And I believe, in this life,
我們雖無力改變自己離去的時間和去處
we have no power to alter where or when we go,
但是我們可以對彼此說幾句話
but we can say things to each other.
有時我們剩下的就只剩語言了
Sometimes, words are all we have left.
你跟奧登上尉說再見了嗎
Have you said goodbye to captain Alden?
我不知道自己能否承受...
I'm not sure I can bear to...
尤其是考慮到...
Especially given how much --
此事我有多大的責任
How much blame may lie on my shoulders.
但是你一如既往地言語睿智
But, as usual, you speak with more wisdom
你的話比歷史上任何事都有道理
than all of the mathers in history combined.
再見  先生
Good day, sir.
-父親  -你去哪里了
- Father - Where have you been?
買東西去了
Shopping.
現在的東西應該能夠我們
I believe I have everything we shall need
存活一周有余了
to survive for a week or more.
存活  存活什么
Survive? Survive what?
過來
This way.
來  幫我一把  親愛的
Here. Give me a hand with this, dear.
怎么  以前沒拿過活鳥嗎
What's the matter? Haven't you ever held a live bird before?
是沒有
No, I-I haven't.
握緊一點
Well, a little -- little tighter.
來  能感受到鳥的心跳嗎
Here. Can you feel its heart beating?
能感受到
Yes, I can.
沒事  不用害怕
Don't worry. There's nothing to be frightened of.
來
Come.
不  不能再死人了
No! No more will die.
此事因我而起  就由我結束
This began with me, and I shall be the one to end it.
安靜
Silence!
否則我就讓你們跟蘿絲一個下場
Or I shall deal with you as I dealt with Rose.
你們以后不許妨礙我  永遠都不許
No longer will you stand in my way -- not now, not ever.
我要離開塞勒姆  我以后再也不回來了
I'm leaving Salem, and I am never coming back.
我走后你們怎樣隨你們
You may do as you like when I'm gone,
但是你們不準跟著我  以后也不許妨礙我
but you will not follow me or hinder me in the years ahead.
不可能  你是被選中之人
那就換人
Then unchoose me.
換霍爾治安官掌權吧
Put magistrate Hale in charge.
他們家族歷史悠久  而且還有新的繼承人
His line is ancient, and yet still springs green a new heir.
但你是被選中之人  是我們創造之人
不  我不是
No, I'm not the one.
我只是你們半路選中的一個人而已
I was just a black rose you grafted to your vine,
現在我受夠了
and I've had enough --
受夠了鮮血和死亡
Enough blood and death --
我馬上就自由了
And I will be free.
找到緹圖芭  告訴她是時候了
我的兒子
Ah, my son...
帶著他一如既往的
with his customary expression
宿醉不醒又疑惑不解的神情
of befuddlement and utter incomprehension.
怎么了  父親
What's happened, father?
你已經把他帶走處決了嗎
Have you taken him off and killed him already,
連最后的遺言和禱告都沒有
without the benefit of final words or prayers
更沒有目擊者
or -- or witnesses?
當然沒有
Of course not.
我會對一個無辜之人做這種事嗎
Would I do such a thing to an innocent man?
我從沒懷疑過約翰·奧登無辜與否
You see, I never doubted John Alden's innocence.
雖然我知道他是個載譽過度的人
Just as I know that he is a man of excessive personal honor,
但我從沒懷疑過
I never doubted the fact that
他一定有充足合理的理由殺死那些人
he had ample and good reason for killing whoever he did kill.
你這是諷刺我
You mock me, sir.
我沒有
No, I do not.
你以為我不明白
Do you think that I don't know that
奧登不比你我多出什么邪術或者超能力嗎
Alden has no more malefic or sulfuric power than you or I?
奧登是個叛徒  殺人犯
Alden is a traitor, he is a murderer,
思想放縱的異教徒
he is a free-thinking heretic,
他是個酒鬼  道德敗壞
He is a drinker, a man of loose morals,
他犯有驕縱之罪
and he is guilty of the sin of pride,
但他絕不是巫師
but a witch -- not at all.
但是  他愛上了一個巫師
However, he is in love with a witch,
更重要的是  這個巫師也愛他
and more importantly, a witch is in love with him.
你是說瑪麗·西布里  她是巫師
You mean Mary Sibley? A witch?
信不信由你
Believe it or not, as you choose.
但這是真的
Nevertheless, it is true.
塞勒姆最重要的女人  竟是巫師嗎
The most important woman in Salem -- a witch?
你有任何證據嗎
Have you any proof, any evidence?
現在還沒有
At present, I have none.
然而  當她和那個被她施法
However, when she is apprehended with her lover,
越獄的愛人一起被逮捕之時
a man she has freed from a locked jail cell with magic,
我會抓她個正著
I'll have her dead to rights.
你
You.
我吩咐的都辦好了嗎
Have you done as I told you?
是的先生  撕成兩半
Yes, sir. Tore it into two.
帶進牢房時  偷塞了半塊在他的口袋里
Snuck half into his pocket as I led him to his cell.
另一半在這兒
The other half, here.
讓獵狗嗅著血  追上他
Blood the hounds. Run him down.
千萬要小心
Heed me carefully --
有人與他同行  這兩人都極度危險
someone will be with him, and they're both very dangerous,
切勿試圖抓捕  或是把他們帶回來
so do not attempt to capture them or bring them back,
彼時彼刻就地正法
but execute them then and there,
兩人都是  就地正法
on the spot -- both of them.
-我授權予你  -先生
- You have my authority to do this. - Sir.
現在去吧  走吧
Now, off with you. Go on.
我懇請您把他們帶回來公正審判
Sir, I plead with you to bring them back for a fair trial.
不必審判了
There's no need for a trial.
這是我們僅有唯一的機會
This is our one and only opportunity
能阻止他們企圖帶來的大規模死亡
to avert the great death that they intend for us.
我沒得選擇  巫師今晚必須死
I have no choice in this. The witch will die tonight.
這個地方存在多久了
How long has this been here?
自我建成這房子之日
Since I built the house.
除非你學會找個真正的藏身之所
You do not survive all that I have survived
否則你的歷練還是比不上我
without knowing how to keep a true hiding place.
這間屋子  只有血印可以開啟
This room, whose door only blood can open,
這是我們的避難所
is our sanctuary.
你在這里很安全
You'll be safe here.
我們得在這里待多久
How long must we stay inside?
至少一周  風才能吹凈空氣
I think at least a week before the winds cleanse the air.
它能告訴我們什么時候開始
And this is how we will know it has begun.
外面有什么大難當頭
What disaster unfolds outside
讓我們必須得躲在這里
that we must cower from in here?
今晚  塞勒姆附近會釋放瘟疫
Tonight, there will be a plague released near Salem,
瘟疫將降臨清教徒的家
A pox upon the puritan house.
只有體內流淌著巫師之血
Only those who carry the witch blood in their veins
或是沾染到巫師之血的人
or are touched by it
才能從瘟疫中幸存
will be safe from this pox.
那我也會死掉
Then I will die of it, too.
柯頓·麥哲檢查過  我不是巫師
Cotton Mather examined me. I'm no witch.
真的嗎
Really?
那他作為一個巫師獵手
Then he is an even more incompetent witchfinder
比我想像中更不稱職
than I thought.
四周看看  你認出什么來了嗎
Look around. Don't you recognize anything here?
你還很小的時候  我經常帶你來這兒
When you were very little, I brought you here often,
你生活的伊始并非是個該死的清教徒
that you might not begin your life as a damned puritan,
無法聆聽樂曲之聲
without the sounds, the music in your ears,
或是無法得見美術之彩的清教徒
or all the colors of art in your eyes.
這里
Here.
這是你三歲的時候畫的
You drew that when you were 3.
這個
This.
這是你的最愛
Well, that was your favorite.
我雕給你的
I carved it for you.
但為什么...為什么我不記得了
But why -- why can't I remember?
因為我得抹去你的記憶
Because I had to take away your memories
直到你做好準備  現在你準備好了
Until you were ready for them, but now you are.
是的  我記得
I do. I do remember.
可我記得它在跳舞
But...I remember it dancing.
它確實在為你而舞
It did dance for you.
是你令它起舞
You made it dance.
我
I?
看著它
Look at it.
用你的心靈之眼  你會看到它在跳舞
And in your mind's eye, see it dancing.
喬治  我要錯過
Oh, George, I shall miss
你的精彩演講了
The dazzle and wit of your conversation.
你知道今晚是什么日子嗎  喬治
Do you know what tonight is, George?
今晚是你此生最幸運的日子
It's the luckiest night of your life.
你不會知道你離毀滅有多近
You'll never know how close you all came to utter destruction.
你曾奪走了我所有重要的東西
You once took away from me everything that meant anything.
今晚  我終于能將其全部奪回
But tonight, I shall finally have it all back.
你說的一點沒錯
Truer than you know...
小姐
...mistress.
你來干什么  叛徒
What do you want here, traitor?
我  叛徒
I? Traitor?
我忍受了那個變態
I, who have endured the worst
施加給我的無數痛苦  只為了保護你
That sick man could inflict upon my flesh to protect you?
我可不這么認為
I think not.
是你背叛了那些養育過你的人
'tis you who have betrayed those who nurtured you,
你背棄了這么多年來
You who have turned your back
我們苦心計劃的一切
On everything we have planned these long years.
不
No.
我離開不是為了背叛  而是為了...
No, I'm leaving not to betray, but to be true...
可能是此生頭一次...做回我自己
Perhaps for the first time... to myself.
你哪也不準去
You are going nowhere.
七年前  兩個女孩走入了樹林
Seven years ago, two girls walked into the woods.
在那里  其中一人許下誓言
There, one of them made a vow.
為封印那個誓言  她奉獻了最為寶貴的東西
To seal that vow, she offered up a most precious thing...
她腹中的小生命
The life she carried within.
不用提醒我那個黑暗的夜晚
No need to remind me of that dark night.
我永遠無法將它從記憶中抹除
I shall never be free of its memory.
不
No.
你不可能忘記自己根本沒有全然了解的事
You cannot forget what you have never really known.
你就沒問過自己
Have you never asked yourself,
沒懷疑過那晚真正發生了什么
Never wondered what really happened that night,
沒想過你腹中的生命到底去哪了嗎
Where the life that swelled your belly went?
那晚沒有誕生
Nothing is created.
也沒有毀滅
Nothing is destroyed.
一切只是轉化而已
All is only ever transformed.
打開吧
Open it.
我的孩子
My child...
還活著
lives?
目前還活著  看你怎么選了
For now, depending on your choice.
這  這只是個為了控制我的邪惡詭計
This... this is some foul trick in order to control me.
不  那晚你并沒殺死那個孩子
No, you did not kill the child that night.
你把它交給了我們侍奉的暗夜之王
You gave him to the dark lord we serve,
這孩子一直被小心呵護著
And this child has been treasured
這是千年來的頭一遭
Like no other in a thousand years.
他什么也不缺  除了他的母親
He has lacked for nothing... except his mother.
你想要我怎樣
What do you want from me?
只要做你曾起誓要做的事
Only what you have vowed to do.
完成大祭典  一切就都會安好
Complete the grand rite, and all shall be well.
若我不肯呢
And if I do not?
延遲的犧牲會帶來更大的力量
A sacrifice deferred is yet more powerful...
尤其是血親的犧牲
Especially a blood sacrifice.
給我聽好  怪物
Hear me well, foul creature.
我將最后一次任你擺布
You have manipulated me for the last time.
我會完成大祭典
I will complete your grand rite.
等一切完成  我發誓  你會付出代價
But when it is done, I swear to you, you will pay.
我們都別無選擇  瑪麗
We must all live without choices, Mary.
你應該最有體會
You know that best of all.
他不見了
He's gone.
奧登上尉不見了
Captain Alden's missing.
是你干的嗎
Was it you?
我說過我不會讓他被絞死
I told you I would not let him hang.
謝謝  瑪麗
Thank you, Mary.
謝謝
Thank you.
真美
It's beautiful.
是啊
Yes. It is.
這是什么
What is it?
死亡
Death.
這是件不祥之物
It's a bad thing,
需要埋葬到不祥之地去
And it needs to go to a bad place.
我任你差遣
Then I'm your man.
給
Here.
這太多了
That's a fortune.
一點小錢
Several fortunes, actually...
親愛的艾薩克  你肯做這件事
Far less than you deserve, sweet Isaac,
其實應該得到更多
For doing such a job.
你可以用這些錢開始新的生活
You can start a new life with it,
一個與你的美好心靈相匹配的生活
One as good as your good heart deserves.
謝謝你
Thank you.
艾薩克  仔細聽著
Isaac, listen carefully.
最重要的事就是  一旦將它放下后
The most important thing is that, when you leave it,
你就繼續前行  遠走高飛  越快越好
you keep going -- far away and quickly.
波士頓  紐約  弗吉尼亞
Boston, New York, Virginia
有多遠走多遠
just keep going.
還有一件事
And one more thing --
你離開小鎮之時
on your way out of town,
把這封信交給柯頓·麥哲
deliver this letter to Cotton Mather.
我再也不會見到您了  是嗎
I shall never see you again, will I?
不  我想不會了
No. No, I expect not.
我很難過
That makes me very sad.
你和上尉是我僅有的
Y-you and the captain are the closest things
最接近朋友的人
to friends I ever had...
除了我曾經知熟悉的一匹馬
Except for a horse I once knew,
但是她死了
but she died.
你應該買一匹新馬
You shall buy a new horse,
一整個馬隊
a whole team of them.
你應該結交新朋友
And you shall make new friends.
這是重生之地
This is the land of second chances.
就像你和約翰·奧登嗎
Like you and John Alden?
你們也會重獲新生嗎
W-will you get your second chance?
是的
Yes.
是的  我想我們會的
Yes, I expect we will.
誰在這兒
Who is here?
是巴比倫大淫婦嗎
Is it the whore of Babylon?
親愛的英克里斯
Oh, dear Increase --
你是如此正確
So terribly right
又如此錯誤
and so terribly wrong.
我能親眼所見自己有多正確
I can see before my eyes how right I was.
你黑暗的光環越發明亮了
Your darkling glow burns brighter than ever...
女巫
witch.
先生
Sir.
給你的
For you.
是什么
What is it?
我不知道
No idea.
西布里夫人讓我交給你的
Mrs. Sibley asked me to give it you.
現在我得走了  因為路途遙遠
Now I must go, for the road is long,
而我的腿卻沒那么長
and...my legs are not.
告訴我  實話實說
Tell me, exactly.
我錯在哪兒了
How was I wrong?
你以為愛情會是我的死穴
You thought love would be my undoing,
我會和情人在叢林里相會
that I would be in the woods with my lover,
然后你就在那兒不費吹灰之力干掉我
and you would kill me there without a trial,
我的大祭典就這樣結束了
thus ending my grand rite.
我跟你分享一個
I will share with you the secret
你和你等族類數世紀以來苦苦尋覓無果的秘密
that you and your kind have sought in vain for centuries --
無辜者的鮮血
innocent blood.
13個無辜的犧牲者
13 innocent sacrifices,
當最后一滴血流下來的時候
and when the last is spilled,
惡靈就會打開
our malum opens,
釋放出它內藏的紅色死亡
unleashing the red death it contains within it.
但是在過去五百年間
And yet, not once in the last 500 years
我們竟沒有一次成功過
have we succeeded...
直到我出現他們才意識到
Until I came along and realized
我們根本不必親自動手來
we needn't spill a single drop of
獲取無辜者的鮮血
innocent blood ourselves --
至少當我們有恐懼又狂熱的清教徒時不必
not when we had fearful and fanatical puritans
他們十分樂意替我們代勞
all too ready to do it for us.
所以你給了我們吉爾斯·科里
So you gave us Giles Corey,
布里奇特·畢謝普
Bridget Bishop...
巴克一家還有其他人
the Barkers, and others,
當然了  還有那些可憐被騙的姑娘們
and of course, those poor, deceived girls --
成桶成桶的無辜者之血
innocent blood by the buckets.
現如今正值
And now here we are,
狩獵滿月之夜
night of full hunter's moon.
12個無辜者已死
12 innocents dead,
落月之前只需再有一個無辜者犧牲
and only one more required before moonfall.
我先殺了你就不會有人犧牲
Not if I kill you first.
是啊  殺掉那個開始大祭典的女巫
Oh, yes, kill the witch who began this grand rite,
你就可以避免這場無盡的死亡
and you might yet avert the great death to come.
祝你好運
Good luck with that.
英克里斯
Oh, Increase.
這點能耐可不夠
You're gonna have to do so much better than that.
不過我向你保證
But I will make you a promise.
一切會在這里結束  就在這屋里  現在
It will end here, in this room, right now.
那邊的  站住
You there! Stop!
你做了正確的事  艾薩克
You've done the right thing, Isaac...
替她卸下了如此重負
taking such a load off her hand.
瑪麗說把它放在老樹這里
Mary said to put it here in the old tree.
這樣不對
This ain't right.
Oh, this ain't right.
任何一個傻瓜都可以感覺到
Any fool can feel that,
甚至是我這個傻瓜
even this fool.
她說過你是死神
She said you were death.
我要把你放在死人該去的地方
I'm gonna put you where the dead belong.
你比你所獵殺的好不到哪去
You are no better than those you hunt.
不  你更加的可惡
No, you're far worse.
一個女巫  就像頭狼
A witch, like a wolf,
不會折磨她的獻祭者
doesn't torture her sacrifice.
只有牧師和審判官會這么做
Only priests and inquisitors do that.
也許你可以說服自己
Perhaps you can convince yourself
認為正與邪之間有那么一點區別
that there is scant difference between good and evil,
但那是不可能的
but I know better.
你有沒有想過
Did it ever occur to you
我們獲得的黑暗力量正是
that the dark power we gain is precisely that
你認為可以從自身驅除的那部分
which you think you can expel from yourself?
你什么都不懂  怪物
You know nothing, creature.
今天這里發生的一切只能證明
Whatever happens here today only proves
我所相信的  是正確的
that what I believe...is true.
父親
Father!
柯頓
Cotton.
感謝上帝  艾薩克找到了你
Thank god Isaac found you.
幫幫我  你父親  他瘋了
Help me. Your father -- he's gone mad!
父親  你做了什么
Father, what have you done?!
我  我什么都沒做
I? I've done nothing.
這妖婦自己找上門來的
This succubus has come to me.
她在玩弄你的理智
She's playing with your mind.
她自己坐上那把椅子的
She has put herself into that chair!
什么
What?!
怎么會
How?
他是個惡魔
He is a devil.
他是個瘋狂的惡魔  先生
Oh, he's a mad devil, sir!
父親  你說瑪麗·西布里是女巫
Father, you said Mary Sibley was a witch.
她就是女巫
She is a witch.
那為什么她不在林子里  父親
Then why is she not in the woods, father,
沒去救奧登上尉  就像你說的那樣
saving Captain Alden, as you said she would be?!
我沒時間回答你愚蠢的問題
I have no time for your idiotic question
更不需要你可惡的質疑
and less for your infernal doubt!
你的偉大計劃其實根本什么都不是
Your great plan has proven nothing!
現在你又要折磨一位無辜的婦女
Now you resort to torturing an innocent woman
來從她口中逼出不實的供詞嗎
to obtain some kind of false confession from her?!
你瞎到看不到了嗎
Are you too blind to see?!
看啊  她都不在那里
Look -- she is not even there!
她不過是一個幻影
She is a mere phantasm!
父親
Father!
她是個幽靈
She is a specter!
父親  我恐怕您已經失去理性
Father, I fear you have lost your reason.
而你  孩子
And you, boy --
你從未有過理性  你個可憐的廢物
You have never had any reason, you pathetic failure.
這賤人現在就得死
This bitch dies now!
不  求你  不要
No, please, no, no.
柯頓  柯頓
Cotton. Cotton.
你做了什么
W-what have you done?
你這個蠢孩子
You foolish boy.
你  柯頓  柯頓
You -- Cotton. Cotton.
上帝
God.
看在上帝的份上
For god's sake...
殺了女巫
Kill the witch.
我殺了他
I have killed him.
我不  我不明白
I don't -- I don't understand.
那是怎么  你是怎么來到這的
How did it -- how do you come to be here?
他把我從屋里拖出來
He dragged me from my rooms.
他打算折磨我
He was going to torture me...
至死
to death.
我必須去尋求幫助
I must call for help.
不不  現在尋找幫助已經沒用了
No. No, there's no help for it now.
但我必須告訴別人
But I must tell someone.
我必須告訴別人我所做的事情
I must tell someone what I've done.
不
No.
我必須告訴別人我所做的事情
I must tell someone what I've done!
不  你會毀了你的家族
No, you would ruin your family --
麥哲家族的名聲
the very name of Mather.
我不會告訴任何人他所要做的事
I will tell no one what he tried to do,
或是你所做的事
nor what you did.
但是你必須離開了  柯頓
But you must leave, Cotton.
馬上去波士頓  就在今晚  立刻出發
Go to Boston now, tonight, immediately.
那  那他怎么辦
What -- what about him?
最好讓他們在你走了之后再發現他
Better they find him here after you are gone.
他們會認為是奧登的支持者干的
They will think those that support Alden got to him --
或者是巫師們
or even witches.
馬上走吧
Now go!
親愛的英克里斯
Oh, dear Increase.
我真希望你還活著  能知道
I hope you're alive enough to know
你被賦予了怎樣的殊榮
what an honor you've been granted.
這是多么的榮耀
Oh, such an honor...
成為我們第十三位受害者
...to be our 13th victim.
我們偉大的儀式現已完成
Our grand rite now is done.
血暗黎明即將到來
Blood-dim dawn now shall come.
月與日之力即將點燃
Powers of moon and sun ignite.
所有軀殼將在夜晚中發抖
All flesh trembles at the sight.
十三冤魂獻與大地
13 souls fed to hungry earth
開啟黑暗領主之誕生
Opens the way for our dark lord's birth.
開始了
It's begun.
我真心以為瑪麗會在最后一刻
I honestly didn't think Mary would be able
下不了手
to do it in the end.
瑪麗
Mary?
瑪麗·西布里嗎
Mary Sibley?
她也是你們的一員
She is one of you?
我們的一員
One of us?
不  遠不止這樣  親愛的
Oh, far more than that, dear.
無論是好是壞
For better or worse,
她都是我們中的第一人
she is the first among us.
是她策劃的這一切
She is behind all this?
就是她這個女巫
She, a witch,
以巫師為名
killed all those innocents,
殺死了布里奇特
killed...Bridget,
殺死了這么多無辜者
as a witch?
不錯  正是她的主意
Indeed, it was her idea
讓清教徒自己雙手奉上我們所需的獻祭
to use the puritans to sacrifice themselves for us --
一個危險卻富有創意的想法
an inspired, if dangerous idea.
為什么出太陽了
Why has the sun come out?
外面到底在發生什么
What is going on outside?
死亡  死亡正在逼近
Death. Death is happening.
你為何不試著去阻止這一切發生
Then why aren't you trying to stop it?
為什么我們要躲在里面
Why are we in here,
而我們的朋友鄰居卻在外面慘死
while outside, our friends and neighbors perish?
一切都太遲了
It's too late for that.
現在我們只能靜候瘟疫散去  然后出去照料幸存者
Now we can only wait and then tend to the survivors.
幸存者
Survivors?
不  我受夠了
I will have none of this.
不管那是什么
Whatever it is,
我更情愿跟那些受難者待在一起
I would rather be with those that suffer it,
而不是跟這些始作俑者
not those that perpetrate it.
把門打開
Open the door.
門已經被封印
It is sealed.
只有用更多的血才能打開
Only more blood will open it now.
快給我打開
Open!
我說過了  只有血祭
I told you -- only blood.
那就用我的血
Then my blood...
-安  住手  -不要
- Anne, stop! Stop! - No!
-停下  快停下  -不
- Stop! Stop it! - No!
讓我出去
Let me out!
我說了  給我停下
I said stop it!
我不是你
I am not you.
我也不像你
I am not like you.
我不是女巫
I am not a witch!
我不是你
I am not you!
去見你的地獄之主吧
Off to meet thy maker.
許多人相信  人死后靈魂仍會徘徊于世
Most agree the soul lingers for some time,
就在尸體不遠處
very close to where the body lies.
它能看見  聽見  并感受到一切發生之事
It sees and hears and feels keenly what happens.
我很高興
I'm glad of that --
你死后仍將為即將發生之事所困
glad you'll suffer through what's still about to happen.
你精心培育的這群禽獸
How good of you to train these fine animals
最終渴求的卻是你的鮮血
to lust for your own blood.
你會得到你應有的下場
It guarantees you the burial you deserve.
野狗會將你吞食殆盡
The dogs will eat their fill of you
然后將你的尸骨排泄在這亂葬崗
and shit your remains out in the crags.
你做到了
You did it,
很快  紅色死亡將籠罩塞勒姆
And soon, the red death will destroy Salem.
多虧了你
No thanks to you.
不得不說  我確實幫了你不少
I have been much help, I would say.
現在  我有更多的東西要給你
And now I have even more to give.
跟我來
Come.
現在
Now...
要知道  孩子們
...you see, children,
只有殺死羅斯
only by killing the rose
暗夜女王
will the queen of the night
才能成為真正的女王
really become the queen of the night.
但那全能的女王卻渾然不知
Little did that mighty queen know
她的一切計劃
that all her plans
即將被徹底逆轉
would be turned upside down.
是的  殺死蘿絲的
Yes, that wasn't really the true queen of the night
并不是真正的暗夜女王
who beheaded the rose.
是我
That was me.
是我殺死了蘿絲
I beheaded the rose.
盡管瑪麗·西布里還未察覺
Though Mary Sibley knows it not yet,
但我才是真正的暗夜女王
I am the queen of the night.
她會為她的一切所為付出代價
And she will pay for what she's done.